{
    "subject": "resource/Daniel_Tammet",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "Daniel Tammet was born in London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.914584755897522,
            "question": "Where was Daniel Tammet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076933026313782,
            "question": "When was Daniel Tammet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7048720121383667,
            "question": "Where did Daniel Tammet grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5925805568695068,
            "question": "Is Daniel Tammet British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48377761244773865,
            "question": "What is Daniel Tammet known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2729824185371399,
            "question": "What are some of Daniel Tammet's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26893988251686096,
            "question": "Is Daniel Tammet famous for his talents in a specific field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21240243315696716,
            "question": "Has Daniel Tammet written any books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19280394911766052,
            "question": "What are some challenges that Daniel Tammet has faced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17128506302833557,
            "question": "Does Daniel Tammet have any special abilities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Daniel Tammet was born in London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7757_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges that Daniel Tammet has faced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7757_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Daniel Tammet written any books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7757_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Daniel Tammet famous for his talents in a specific field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7757_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7757_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: While the first document mentions that Daniel Tammet grew up in an English-speaking environment and was born in a working-class suburb of London (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7757/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt), other documents specify different birth locations for him, such as East London, England (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7757/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt) and Barking, Essex, England, UK (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7757/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state, \"Daniel Tammet was born in a working-class suburb of London, England,\" and \"Daniel Tammet was born on January 31, 1979 in Barking, Essex, England, UK.\" Both indicate that Daniel Tammet's birth location is associated with London."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because multiple sources state he was born in a working-class suburb of London, England, on 31 January 1979, or specifically in Barking, Essex, England, UK.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}